Department of Chemistry fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Teaching, 1973 - 1985; F-6-16; 20 cm of textual records
  - Examinations and course outlines, 1980 - 1985; F-6-16-2; 8 cm of textual records
    - Examinations and course outlines - undergraduate 300-400 level, 1980 - 1981; F-6-16-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Examinations and course outlines - graduate, 1980 - 1981; F-6-16-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Examinations and course outlines - undergraduate 000-100 level, 1982 - 1985; F-6-16-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Examinations and course outlines - undergraduate 200 level, 1982 - 1983; F-6-16-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Examinations and course outlines - undergraduate 300 level, 1982 - 1985; F-6-16-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Examinations and course outlines - undergraduate 400 level, 1982 - 1983; F-6-16-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
    - Examinations and course outlines - graduate, 1983 - 1985; F-6-16-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-16)
  - Student cases, 1974 - 1977; F-6-16-3; 2 cm of textual records
    - Student cases, 1974 - 1977; F-6-16-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-17)
  - Teaching loads, 1973 - 1977; F-6-16-4; 2 cm of textual records
    - Teaching loads, 1973 - 1977; F-6-16-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-17)
- Theoretical Science Institute, 1979 - 1984; F-6-17; 2 cm of textual records
  The Theoretical Science Institute was an organization of a number of theoreticians in the Biology, Chemistry and Mathematics Departments at S.F.U. The purpose of the Institute was to provide a better research environment in theoretical Chemistry and Physics and certain areas of Applied Mathematics, in order to improve the University's research effort and to attract high calibre sabbatical visitors, post-doctoral fellows and graduate students.
  Series consists of materials related to proposals for the establishment of the Institute, including correspondence.
  Theoretical Science Institute
  - Theoretical Science Institute, 1979 - 1984; F-6-17-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-17)
- Faculty of Science, 1968 - 1986; F-6-18; 45 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to Department involvement in committees of the Faculty of Science. These committees include the Biochemistry Curriculum Committee, Faculty Graduate Curriculum Committee, Faculty of Science Executive Committee, and the Faculty of Science Undergraduate Committee. It includes agenda, minutes, correspondence and related papers.
  - Committees, 1968 - 1986; F-6-18-1; 23 cm of textual records
    Biochemistry Committee; Faculty of Science Graduate Studies Committee; Faculty of Science Executive Committee; Faculty of Science Undergraduate Curriculum Committee
    - Biochemistry Curriculum Committee, 1970 - 1976; F-6-18-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-17)
    - Faculty Graduate Curriculum Committee, 1984 - 1985; F-6-18-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-17)
    - Faculty Graduate Curriculum Committee, 1983 - 1984; F-6-18-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-17)
    - Faculty Graduate Curriculum Committee, 1982 - 1983; F-6-18-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-17)
    - Faculty Graduate Studies Committee, 1975 - 1977; F-6-18-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-18)
    - Faculty Graduate Studies Committee, 1978; F-6-18-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-18)
    - Faculty Graduate Studies Committee, 1986; F-6-18-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 6-18)
    - Faculty of Science Executive Committee, 1972 - 1973; F-6-18-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 6-18)
    - Faculty of Science Executive Committee, 1973 - 1975; F-6-18-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 6-18)
    - Faculty of Science Executive Committee, 1971; F-6-18-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 6-18)
    - Faculty of Science Executive Committee, 1971; F-6-18-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 6-18)
    - Faculty of Science Executive Committee, 1970 - 1971; F-6-18-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 6-18)
    - Faculty of Science Executive Committee, 1968 - 1970; F-6-18-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 6-19)
    - Faculty of Science Undergraduate Committee, 1974 - 1977; F-6-18-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 6-19)
  - Meetings, 1976 - 1985; F-6-18-2; 22 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Science. Chairmen's Meetings; Faculty of Science. Faculty Meeting
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1978 - 1980; F-6-18-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 6-19)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1978 - 1979; F-6-18-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 6-19)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1977 - 1978; F-6-18-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 6-19)
    - Faculty of Science Minutes of Meetings, 1976; F-6-18-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 6-19)
    - Faculty of Science Minutes of Meetings, 1977; F-6-18-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 6-19)
    - Faculty of Science Minutes of Meetings, 1978; F-6-18-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 6-19)
    - Faculty of Science Minutes of Meetings, 1979; F-6-18-2-0-7 (Archival box - small 6-20)
    - Faculty of Science Minutes of Meetings, 1980; F-6-18-2-0-8 (Archival box - small 6-20)
    - Faculty of Science Minutes of Meetings - October 15, 1985; F-6-18-2-0-9 (Archival box - small 6-20)
    - Faculty of Science Minutes of Meetings - October 15, 1985; F-6-18-2-0-10 (Archival box - small 6-20)